翻译校对       Syura
日  听      HARERE
日听校对       Syura
翻译        Mam
时间轴       黑猫与牛奶
压制      娜夏
OP&ED       葉隠
Syura
诸神字幕组
At midnight, the carriage
was sure to become a pumpkin.
その馬車は真夜中になると
きっとカボチャになっちゃう
However,
ただし　魔法の呪文を唱えたのは
it wasn't some old witch
who had cast this spell.
魔女のおばあさんじゃない
All right,
では　次の議題に移りましょう
let's move on to the next
item on the agenda.
I would like to discuss
the plans for next week.
来週の企画について  話し合いたいと思います
"Class 1-A Representative, Kazukiyo Soga"
Plans?
企画
ハロウィンだよ
Halloween.
Haruhi- kun, you became an honor
student here starting in high school,
ハルヒ君は高等部からの特待生だから
"Vice-Representative, Momoka Kurakano"
so you wouldn't know about it, huh?
ご存知ありませんわね
Here at Ouran, during the grading
of our in-school trial exams,
この桜蘭では　校内模試の採点とかぶる
we're allowed to take off until
the last day of October every year,
10月の末日までは
毎年授業はお休み
and hold costume parties
here on campus.
学院内での仮装パーティーが許可されているんです
Also, to promote camaraderie,
さらには親睦を目的に
we are allowed to take a whole day
まる一日をクラスのイベントで
and use it however we like,
as a class event.
好きに使っていいことになっています
An event?
イベント
Well, usually, we...
ま　つっても大抵はさ
...have tea parties,
watch movies, and so on.
お茶会とか　映画上映とかだけどね
Not good enough! Not good enough!
Not good enough!!
あまい　あまい　あまいですわ
Halloween!
ハロウィン
It's the day that signals the end
of summer, and the start of winter.
それは夏の終わりと冬の始まりを告げる日
Halloween...
ハロウィン
The day when people come out against
the spirits and devils that come by,
訪れる使者や悪魔に人々は同じ姿を持って対抗する日
by making themselves look like them.
Halloween...
ハロウィン
It also, in time,
そしてそれはやがて
became a festival of dressing up
in costumes, and playing pranks.
仮装といたずらのお祭りになったのだと申します
Some people don't wait for permission
to have costume parties...
仮装パーティーの許可なんかなくても
...and engage in cosplay all year round.
年中コスプレしている人がいますよ
So, what's with that uniform?
で　その制服何
"Rewind button"
To tell you the truth, this is
the uniform for the girl characters
なにを隠そう
これは来年発売予定のウキドキメモリアルⅡに登場する
who will be appearing
in "Uki-doki Memorial 2,"
女子キャラ用の制服なのですわ
which isn't scheduled
to come out until next spring.
"Through bribery, she obtained
top-secret information"
I obtained some advance, unannounced
information, and made this.
未発表の情報を先取りして
作ってみましたの
Hoshakuji- san, we're having homeroom.
宝積寺さん　ホームルーム中です
Please come down off of the desk.
机の上から降りてください
コスプレしてお茶など
Cosplaying and having tea parties
is something we do all
the time in the Host Club.
ホスト部ではいつもやっていること
What good is having Halloween
without any further stimulation?
さらなる刺激がなくて
何がハロウィンでしょう　でしょう　でしょう
...- lation? ...- lation?
Um, this is to be a class event.
いや　これはクラスのイベントだから
I hereby propose
私はここに
that we have a Halloween special
test-of-courage tournament!
ハロウィンスペシャル
肝試し大会を
提案いたします
"Halloween Test-of-Courage Tournament"
A Halloween special...
ハロウィンスペシャル
...test-of-courage tournament?
肝試し大会
We'll ask the superintendent
to open the school to us at night.
理事長にお願いして
夜の校舎を開放していただくのです
Then, we all take turns dressing up
as monsters, and scaring each other.
そしてみんなで交代でお化けになって脅かし合う
It will make for wonderfully
high-spirited, exciting communication!
それはそれは素晴らしきドキドキコミュニケーションでございますわ
Great! That sounds great! We're in!
いい　それいい　それ乗った
I like the part about...
夜の学校ってとこが
...the school, at night.
気に入ったね
The school at night, huh?
夜の学校か
That could be kind of exciting, all right.
確かにちょっとドキドキするかも
すげぇこわい作戦思いついた
I just thought of a really scary idea!
Everyone takes turns as frighteners,
and one-by-one, we test our courage!
みんなが脅かし役になって
一人ずつ順番に肝試しをやるのね
Going one at a time wouldn't
be very efficient, would it?
一人ずつじゃ効率悪いんじゃないかな
We also have to consider
time allocation...
時間配分も考えないと
There should be at least
three or four at a time.
せめて三四人ずつね
It would be better if
it were really scary, right?
ウーンと怖いのがいいわよね
For anyone who runs out
in the middle of it...
途中で逃げ出したやつは
...we'll have them featured on
the front page of the school paper
"Captain of All Cowards,
1-A's Kazukiyo Soga"
臆病大臣として
校内新聞の一面を飾っていただくことにしよう
- Seconded!
賛成
Okay then, um...
それでは　えっと
does anyone have any objection
to a majority vote?
この多数決に異論のある人はいませんか
Is anyone opposed?
反対の人はいませんか
Is there really no one?
本当にいませんか
Very well then,
for 1-A's class event...
それでは　一年A組のクラスイベントは
"Settled"
...we would like to settle
on the Halloween special
宝積寺さんの提案した
ハロウィンスペシャル肝試しに決定したいと思います
test of courage proposed
by Hoshakuji- san.
"Music Room #3"
"The Host Club is now
open for business"
Trick or treat.
トリック・オア・トリート
Give me some candy,
or I'll play a prank on you.
おやつをくれないと
いたずらしちゃうぞ
Halloween isn't until next week,
but at the Host Club,
ハロウィンは来週ですが
我がホスト部は今日から
a special Halloween week begins today.
スペシャルハロウィンウィークとなります
Tamaki- kun, you're
a vampire this year, right?
環君　今年はヴァンパイアですのね
You look just fantastic.
とっても素敵
Can I get a treat from you,
in the form of some blood?
僕に血という名のおやつをいただけますか
I cannot give you any.
So please, play your trick.
差し上げません
ですから　いたずらなさってください
Then, here comes the kiss of death.
では　死の口づけを
Me next!
次　私
Hey there.
ウィース
You guys are late.
Hurry up and get changed.
遅いぞお前たち
早く着替えろ
Oh, from now until Halloween day...
あ　僕たちハロウィン当日まで
...we're skipping club activities.
部活休むから
よろしくね
By your leave.
What!?
何
How come?
どうしたの
We have a class event
until Halloween day,
ハロウィン当日にクラスのイベントがあるんで
so we're busy getting ready for that.
そっちの準備が忙しいの
Then it can't be helped.
ならしょうがない
つうわけでよろしく
That being the case, carry on!
Hang in there!
頑張ってね
Wait, wait, why are you
taking Haruhi with you!?
待って待って
なんでハルヒを連れて行く
Well, Haruhi is in our class, after all.
だってハルヒも同じクラスだもん
We're having a special
test-of-courage tournament
夜の学校でスペシャル肝試し大会やるんだもん
at the school, at night.
The school... at night...
夜の…学校
"The Midnight Theatre of Tamaki's Mind"
Wah! I'm scared, Hikaru!
怖いよ光
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
怖いよ　怖いよ　怖い
Sh-sh-sh-sh-sh!
Wah! I'm scared, Kaoru!
怖いよ馨
I'm scared! I'm scared!
怖いよ　怖いよ
Haruhi,
ハルヒ　そんないかがわしい夜のイベントに
are you seriously planning to attend
such an improper nighttime event?
お前は本気で参加するつもりなのか
Well, class camaraderie
is important, and all.
まあ　クラスの親睦も大事ですから
Camaraderie? Camaraderie, you say?
親睦　親睦だと
どんな親睦だ
What kind of camaraderie is that!?
How trampy...
ふしだらな
Letting his little girl go playing around
うちの子に夜遊びさせるなど
at night is something that Daddy...
お父さんは　お父さんは絶対に許しませんよ
something that Daddy absolutely forbids!
There was the magic spell.
これが魔法の呪文だ
We may just be members of a club,
僕たちはただ部活のメンバーだけど
but his highness calls
Haruhi his daughter,
殿はハルヒを娘と呼び
and pictures us as members of his family.
そして僕たちを家族としてイメージしてる
Okay, let's go, Haruhi.
じゃ行こうかハルヒ
Adieu, sir!
アデュー　殿
Hey, wait! Include me in your event, too!
こら待って
そのイベント俺も混ぜろ
Nekozawa- senpai, when did you...
猫沢先輩　いつの間に
I just heard something quite interesting.
これはおもしろいことを聞きました
Is that right? You think
it would be fun, too, Belzenef?
そうですか　ベルゼネフも楽しそうだと思いますか
If it's unfathomable
terror they're after,
底なしの恐怖をお求めなら
those of us in the Black Magic Club
will have to do our part, as well.
我々黒魔術部が一役買わないわけにはいきませんね
By all means,
let us give the 1st-Years
ぜひとも一年生に忘れられないハロウィンを
a Halloween present they won't forget.
プレゼントして差し上げましょう
What should we do about the budget?
予算はどうしましょうね
Once we start going in for the ghost
costumes, there'll be no end to it.
お化けの衣装なんて
凝り始めたらキリがないし
Following the commoners' rule
of keeping it under 300 yen...
そこは庶民ルールで300円以内
...on the cheap will
make things interesting.
チープな方がおもしろい
We might have people who will faint,
気絶する人が出るかもしれないし
- so maybe we should have
a doctor standing by.
- They all seem to be enjoying themselves.
お医者様に待機していただいた方がいいかもしれませんね
なんか楽しそうだなみんな
Huh? Nyctophobia?
暗所恐怖症
Chairman, you can't handle
being in the dark?
委員長暗いとこだめなの
You can add to that horror-movie-phobia,
加えて言うならホラー映画恐怖症
ghost-story-phobia,
怪談話恐怖症
suddenly-being-startled-
by-a-bang-phobia,
いきなりバーンと脅かされるの恐怖症
as well as TV-commercials-
for-scary-movies-phobia.
それからテレビの恐怖映画のCM恐怖症
What is it with those things?
I wish they would stop
何なんだよあれ
いつも前降りなく突然流すのやめてほしいよ
showing them all the time
without giving us any warning.
Where are the human rights
for us scaredy-cats?
怖がりの人権はどうなるんだ
For that matter, why do all
the other classes get to have
っていうか　他のクラスは皆普通にお茶会とかなのに
the usual tea parties and such,
but ours is the only class unanimously
choosing a test of courage!?
なんでうちだけ全員一致で肝試しなんだ
I don't understand the point!
It's autumn already!
もう秋なのに
意味わかんないよ
Chairman, calm down.
委員長落ち着いて
ごめん　藤岡
Sorry, Fujioka.
If you didn't want to,
you could have opposed it.
嫌なら反対すればよかったのに
Chairman, if you spoke up,
we all would have gone along.
委員長が言えば　みんなだって
It's just that doing so would
seem like, as chairman,
なんかそういうの
委員長の権限を振りかざすみたいで嫌だったんだよ
I'm lording my authority over
everyone, so I didn't want to.
That's why I was hoping to be rescued,
だから助けてもらおうと思ったのに
by you, Fujioka!
藤岡に
Like I said, calm down.
だから落ち着いてって
Sorry.
ごめん
How was I supposed to rescue you?
助けるったって　どうやって
I desperately sent out signs to you,
Fujioka, to have you oppose it,
こういうの興味なさそうな藤岡に反対してもらおうと
because you didn't seem like you were
interested in this sort of thing.
必死にサイン送ってたのに
Does anyone have any objection to this
このハロウィンスペシャル肝試し大会に異論のある人は
special Halloween
test-of-courage tournament?
いませんか
Is anyone opposed?
反対の人はいませんか
Is there really no one?
本当にいませんか
If even one person was against it,
一人でも反対があれば
I could have brought
it up for discussion...
議題にできるのに
Sorry, I had no idea.
ごめん　全然気がつかなかった
"Telepathic ability: zero"
I beg you, Fujioka, tomorrow,
be in the same group as me!
頼む藤岡
明日は同じ班になってくれ
I think that somehow,
if I'm at your side,
なんとなく君のそばなら
your presence of mind will spread
to me, and I can remain calm!
その平常心が伝染して
落ち着けるような気がするんだよ
Chairman...
委員長
Also, keep this absolutely
secret from Hikaru and Kaoru.
それとこれは
光と馨にゃ絶対内緒に
Chairman, you're a scaredy-cat?
委員長って怖がりなんだ
Ah, this is where you all are.
ああ　みなさん　ここにいらしたのね
I'm asking who wants to be
in which group right now.
今班分けの希望を伺ってるんですけど
はい　この四人で組みます
Okay! The four of us
will team up together!
Okay, then you four will be B Team.
はい　じゃ四人はBチームね
Good luck to us all, Chairman.
頑張ろうね委員長
This is a disaster!
最悪だ
You poor boy...
お気の毒に
"Halloween"
"...Night"
"Shiver, shiver..."
Do you know, Kaoru, about the story
of the clock tower witch?
知ってたか馨
時計塔の魔女の話
Yeah. Long ago, a girl student
who was dressed up like a witch
ああ　昔ハロウィンの日に
魔女の仮装をした女生徒が
on Halloween took a tumble
from the clock tower.
時計塔から転落して
Ever since, anyone who
sees her on Halloween
以来　ハロウィンにその姿を見た者は
呪われてしまう
is cursed.
S-stop that!
やっ　やめてくれ
Hey, cut it out. What's good is it
to scare someone on your own team?
ちょっとやめなよ
同じチームの人を驚かしてどうすんの
It's our turn to be scaring
the others right now.
だいたい今は驚かし役の方なんだから
But no one has come yet,
and we've got nothing to do.
だってまだ誰も来なくて暇なんだもん
Chairman, pull it together.
委員長　しっかり
It's all right.
Look, I borrowed this book,
大丈夫
ほら　図書室で『怖い状況を切り抜ける方法』って本借りといたから
titled "Ways to Get Through Scary
Situations," from the school library.
Fujioka...
藤岡
Let's see, what have we got in here?
えーとね　なになに
"Ways to cope when dealing with
scary situations: Number 1..."
怖い状況に直面した場合の対処法その一
"Test-of-courage item,
made by Haruhi for 300 yen"
Mm-hmm...
"better known as konjac jelly"
"Just bear through it.
It will be over eventually."
耐えていればいつかは終わる
"Number 2: Chant
'Away, spooks! ' ten times."
その二　バーサレと十回唱える
"Number 3: If you see something,
pretend you didn't."
その三　見えてても見えないふりをする
No! None of those solve anything!
嫌だ
そんなのなんの解決にもなってない
Wah! I'm leaving! Call me Minister
of Pantywaists, or anything else,
もう帰る
臆病大臣でもなんでもいいから帰らしてくれ
just let me out of here!
Hmm, are you sure?
いいのかな　愛しの倉賀野姫に笑われても
Even if it means your dear
Princess Kurakano laughs at you?
Oh yeah? Chairman,
you like Kurakano- san?
委員長って　倉賀野さんのこと好きなんだ
違う　単なる幼馴染みで
N-no! We've simply been
friends since we were little,
and this doesn't have
anything to do with it!
今回のこととは別に関係なくて
We're just childhood friends!
あの　単なる幼馴染みで
Okay, okay, we got it, we got it.
はいはい　分かってる分ってる
Chairman, you said you didn't want
to lord your authority over us...
委員長の権限振りかざすの嫌とか言ってたけど
...but it's really that you
couldn't oppose the plan,
本当は弱気なとこ見せたくなくて
because you didn't want
to look timid, huh?
企画に反対できなかったんだもんね
No. That's not the reason
why I couldn't oppose it.
違う
反対てきなかったのは　そんなんじゃない
I... I just...
僕は　僕はただ
It would be better if it were really
scary, right? ...right? ...right?
ウーンとこわいのがいいわよね
"Fidget fidget"
Huh?
It was because Kurakano- san...
倉賀野さんが
It was because Kurakano- san
seemed to be looking forward
倉賀野さんが肝試し　楽しみにしてるみたいだったから
to this test of courage.
しまった
Oh, crap!
He's pure! He's taken
the pure-hearted line!
ピュアだ　純情路線だ
He's from the land of those
we must not pick on!
いじめてはいけない国の人だ
Ah, our own filthiness
stands out in sharp relief!
ああ　己の汚れが浮き彫りに
"A pure type that is
fair game to pick on"
But, if that's the case, we have
to work with him even more now.
でも　それなら尚更協力してやんなきゃ
Am I imagining things?
気のせいかな
There was some sort of white figure,
outside the window, just now.
今白い影みたいなのが窓の外に
S-stop! Not you too, Fujioka!
What are you talking about!?
やっやめてよ　藤岡まで　何言ってんの
T-this is a sneak attack
by those A Team guys, right?
Aチームの奴らの騙し討ちだな
It's not their turn yet!
Follow the rules, will you!?
まだ順番じゃないだろう
ルールは守れよな
That hurt!
痛い
Nice shooting.
ナイスシュート
That hurt... That hurt...
痛い
It couldn't be...
the clock tower... witch?
まさか　時計塔の魔女
Are you the ones who kicked...
髑髏を蹴ったのは
...my skull?
お前らか
Who's there?
Nnngh...
フンガー　フランケン
Frankenstein...
The wolfman!
狼男
"Wrong"
Chairman, where do you think
you're going? Calm down!
委員長　どこ行く気だよ　落ち着いて
My terror strategy was flawless.
私の恐怖作戦は完璧ですね
Kyoya- kun, you're not joining in?
鏡夜君は参加しないのですか
No, I'm not.
しません
Damn it, we're locked in.
チクショウ　閉じ込められた
Youch... What is this?
Are we some kind of prey?
イッテテ
何だこりゃ　俺らは獲物か
I mean, Kaoru!
っていうか馨
- Where's Kaoru!? Where'd Kaoru go!?
- H-hold on! Don't thrash around, Hikaru!
馨は　馨はどこ
ちょっと　暴れないでよ光
馨
I'm going to cut this net
right now with my scissors.
今　はさみでこの網切るから
"Sewing set"
Oh, Haruhi, I see even
you have a girly side.
ハルヒにも女らしいところが
What do you mean,
"Haruhi, even you have?"
なんだよその「ハルヒにも」ってのは
Hikaru, you've got a smart mouth.
口悪いな光は
What about you? What do you mean,
"Hikaru, you've" got one?
お前こそ　「光は」ってなんだよ
Kaoru isn't any different, is he?
馨だって変わんないだろう
When Kaoru is by himself, he stays
relatively sensible, and calm.
馨は一人だとわりと常識人っぽいし　落ち着いてるよ
Hikaru, when you're by yourself,
you're annoying, and thoughtless.
光は一人でもうるさいし　非常識
Is that so?
そうかよ
Okay, hold still for a minute.
それじゃ　ちょっとじっとしててね
W-why are you positioning
yourself like that...
何　この態勢
Sorry, but I can't move
around any other way.
ごめん　だって他に身動き取れないし
It might be awkward, but
just put up with it a minute.
苦しいかもだけど　ちょっと我慢してよ
Nah... I wouldn't say
"put up with..."
いや　我慢…っていうか
I-I can't allow this!
ゆっ　許せん
If you run out there now,
our plan will be ruined.
ここで飛び出したら
作戦が台無しでしょう
"Science Room"
It's no use. It doesn't
sound like anyone is outside.
だめだ　外だれもいないみたい
This is going too far,
to put it mildly, A Team.
いくらなんでもやり過ぎだろうAチーム
君どっち
Which one are you?
I'm Kaoru. Are you scared to death?
馨だよ　腰抜けた
No, it's like, I got so scared
that it doesn't matter anymore.
いや　なんかもう怖すぎてどうでも良くなっちゃったよ
Ah, man, our plans have
been completely ruined.
ああ　計画丸つぶれだよ
The truth is, we had a whole
heartwarming scenario prepared,
実はさ　倉賀野姫が回ってきたら
where once Princess
Kurakano came around,
さんざん脅かしてさ
そこを委員長に慰めさせてやろうという
we were going to scare her like crazy,
and have you go in
to comfort her, Chairman.
心温まるシナリオを用意してたんだ
Well, I'm grateful to hear that,
but really, it's all right.
いや　ありがたいんだけど　本当にいいんだって
For one thing, Kurakano- san is
more a fan of Fujioka, and all.
だいたい倉賀野さんって　藤岡のファンだしさ
ハルヒ君
Haruhi- kun!
It doesn't look like Fujioka has any
interest in Kurakano- san right now,
藤岡は　今のところ倉賀野さんに興味ないみたいだけど
but before long, they might
fall in love with each other.
そのうち両思いになるかもしれないし
いや　それは神に誓って絶対ありえないから
No, I swear to God, that
definitely will not happen.
Why not?
どうして
It just won't.
どうしても
Still, this might sound
like I'm making excuses,
だけど　いいわけに聞こえるかもしれないけど
but right now, I really don't
feel like doing anything about it.
本当に　今のところどうする気もないんだ
It's fun just being on the class
committee together with Kurakano- san,
倉賀野さんと二人で一緒にクラス委員もやれて楽しいしさ
For now, I don't want to wreck
the relationship we have currently.
当分は今の関係を壊したくないっていうか
So in other words, that's what your
spell on the carriage is, Chairman.
つまりそれは
委員長の馬車の魔法か
Sure, that way of thinking is fine.
確かにそういう考え方もありだよな
If you can keep on running the way
you have been, that's not so bad.
このまま走り続けられれば　悪くない
I'm sure that keeping a family setting,
with fathers and daughters,
父とか娘とかの家族設定は
is his highness's magic spell,
to keep our current relationships
きっと今の関係を壊したくないっていう
from being ruined.
殿の魔法なんだろうな
Huh?
Neither his highness nor we had ever
played with many other friends.
殿も僕らも
今まで大勢の友達と遊ぶとかなかったからさ
He wants to enjoy things the way
they are now as much as he can,
できる限り　今のままで楽しくやりたいってのは
and so do I.
僕だってそうだし
Sorry, what are we talking about?
ごめん　なんの話
But, at some point,
でも　どうせいつかは
there's a good chance that it will
all turn into a muddy pumpkin.
泥沼のカボチャになっちゃう可能性が高いんだけど
Kaoru! Are you in there, Kaoru!?
馨　いるのか馨
Kaoru!
馨
Hikaru!
光
- Hikaru!
- Kaoru!
馨（光）
Huh? Where's Fujioka?
Weren't you together?
あれ　藤岡は　一緒じゃないの
Ah, whoops. I forgot.
"Ah..."
あっ　しまった　忘れてた
Hikaru, no fair! After we got out
of the net, you ran off by yourself!
光　ずるいよ
網抜けたとたん　一人で走ってっちゃうんだもん
Sorry.
ごめん
Ah, they're coming back!
あ　戻ってきた
Oh my, we were so worried
about all of you!
まあ　心配したのよ　みなさん
Where did you go off to,
and leave your post?
どこ行ってたんだよ
持ち場放棄して
We called off the test
of courage to look for you!
肝試し切り上げて探したんだぞ
Huh?
That was all of you playing
tricks on us, right?
そっちが悪さしたせいだろう
Huh? We didn't do anything.
僕らは何も
Aaah!
どうしたの
What's wrong?
Just now, outside the window...
今　窓の外に
There was something white out there!
なにか白いものが
They sure got us.
してやられた
"Everyone in Class 1-A
is a Captain of All Cowards"
That rotten Nekozawa- senpai...
猫沢先輩め
If you look closer,
it's clearly Belzenef, isn't it?
よく見りゃ明らかにベルゼネフじゃん
I heard.
聞きましたわ
Kazukiyo- kun, you're
really a scaredy-cat,
和清君　本当は怖がりなのに
but for the sake of the class,
you put up with this?
クラスのためと思って我慢してくれたんですって
Uh, no, um, well... sorry...
いや　まあ　ごめん
How big of you! I have
a newfound respect for you!
えらいです　私　改めて尊敬します
Nice mood, huh?
いいムードじゃん
I guess the spell on the carriage
can't go on forever after all.
やっぱりいつまでも馬車の魔法が続かないのかな
What are you talking about?
何の話
Hikaru, no fair! After we got out
of the net, you ran off by yourself!
光　ずるいよ
網抜けたとたん　一人で走ってっちゃうんだもん
Sorry.
ごめん
Well, if he ran towards
me in that situation,
まっ　あの状況で僕の方に走ってきちゃううちは
I guess it's still all right.
まだ大丈夫か
Huh?
Nothing, it's my own little joke.
Come on, come on.
いやいや　こっちの話
さあ　行こう行こう
Still, when Hikaru...
でも光が
... starts realizing that he wants
to take the next step forward...
もう一歩先に進みたいって気付き始めちゃったら
Once that happens,
そうしたら僕は
what am I going to do?
どうしようかな
モリ先輩のお弟子さんが
ちょっと待った！
そのお弟子さんって笠田野組四代目
Eh? Mori-senpai has an apprentice?
その筋の人ってことですか
Just a minute! That apprentice
is the Kasanoda Syndicate 4th?
You mean, someone like that?
桜蘭高校ホストクラブ　来週も
Next time, "Mori- senpai Has
an Apprentice Candidate"
お待ちしております
Ouran High School Host Club will
be waiting for you, next week!